Front-end Developer

vermavaibhav452@gmail.com

Ø

H.No. 22/2, Bhikam colony Ballabgarh



https://www.linkedin.com/in/vaibhav-verma-6647b9250

https://github.com/VaibhavVerma844

SUMMARY

As a Front-End Developer is a tech industry professional who specializes in building the front portion of websites that users interact with. Creating User-Friendly Web Pages, Optimizing Applications, designing mobile features, feedback and problem solving, graphics standard and brand consistency.

EDUCATION

DAV Centenary College

Bachelor of Computer Application 2020-2023

Bohra Public School from CBSE

12th in 2020

Bohra Public School

10th in 2018

SKILLS

- AR invoices
- SAP software
- PO report
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- MS Office
- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- GSAP
- BOOTSTRAP
- jQuery
- C++, C
- Pythor
- Data Structure and Algorithms
- Web designing
- Ui /Ux design

CERTIFICATIONS

- In Web Development from Amit Coding Class
- Digital Marketing from Google
- In Photoshop from Amit Coding Class

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Billing and Store Executive

Surya Spring Pvt Ltd | Jan 2023 - Dec 2023

- Generating AR invoices, Stock management from SAP software.
- Managing Records and Data in SAP software.
- Generating PO for purchase order in SAP software.
- Generating purchase order data in SAP software.

Telecaller

SriBalaji Callnet Pvt Ltd | Mar 2024- May 2024

- Sales credit card through calling.
- Support customer service through calling.
- Generate QD for Customer.

Freelancer

Part-time Freelancer | Present

- Generate Portfolio for Client of Devopos Engineer Using html, CSS, javascript and Gsap with responsive view and backend node js.
- Creating a Login from page using html CSS javascript.

PROJECTS

- Creating a Video player using Javascript.
- Creating a Login from page using html CSS javascript.
- Creating a Portfolio using Frontend skills and backend skills.
- Creating a Calculator using Javascript.
- Creating industry level projects through Data structure and Algorithms with C++.
- Finding target through DSA.
- Solve 100+ questions through DSA with C++.